#### Contact

ogunsanyaopeyemi4@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/opeyemiogunsanya (LinkedIn) o-opeyemi.github.io (Personal)

### Top Skills

MySQL

Python (Programming Language)
Arduino

### Certifications

Javascript, Bootstrap, & PHP -Certification for Beginners Scientific Computing with Python

# Opeyemi Ogunsanya

Full stack Web developer | Python Programmer | Electronics Engineer | Arduino programmer

Lagos State, Nigeria

## Summary

Hi I'm Opeyemi Ogunsanya a determined Software Engineer with experience and a student in Electrical/Electronics Engineering. I have impacted in so many lives in the line of Software Engineering, Various tech stack used: Python, JavaScript, React.Js I've also been part of several teams to push great content to the public. I enjoyed bridging the gap between engineering and design to create beautiful results from the design.

## Experience

DAAR Communications Plc Engineer Intern July 2022 - October 2022 (4 months)

RichTechnologies
Information Technology Intern
August 2021 - September 2021 (2 months)
Lagos, Nigeria

Code Warriors
Student Representative
June 2020 - September 2020 (4 months)

### Education

Ajayi Crowther University
Electrical/Electronics Engineering, Electrical and Electronics
Engineering · (2019 - 2024)